favorise.com 2012-05-24

# Privacy policy - Favorise

**Please read carefully the following privacy policy before reading, subscribing to, downloading, uploading, transmitting, copying, reproducing, translating, publishing, altering materials of any kind, posting information, linking to (COLLECTIVELY "USING") any content of this Website in any way.** The content **("Content")** includes the text, graphics, photos, sounds, music, videos, audiovisual combinations, software, scripts or any other materials you may view on, access through, or contribute to the "Website" (also referred to as **"Favorise"** ). Favorise includes the Website at [favorise.com](http://favorise.com/), [favorise.ca](http://favorise.ca/), [favorise.net](http://favorise.net/), [favorise.info](http://favorise.info/), [favorise.us](http://favorise.us/), [favorise.org](http://favorise.org/) and any sub-domain, international version, widget or mobile version. Favorise is the property of FAVORISE INC. By FAVORISE INC. we mean the owners (also referred to as **"we"** , **"us"** and **"our"** ), the employees, the features, and services we make available including Favorise and any other FAVORISE INC. branded websites, sub-domains, international versions, widgets and mobile versions. 

## Comments

When you leave a comment, Favorise is automatically notified and receives IP, WHOIS, and e-mail information pertaining to the Commenter. This Website is hosted in Virginia, USA. Be aware that laws regarding personal information and privacy may differ from your location. 

## Account Information

All the information in your account is public and can be seen by the Website's Users except for your email and password. Do not share your login information or let anyone access your account or make anything that could compromise your user account security. Do not provide information you do not want other people to see. You have to be at least 13 years old in order to use this Website. Parental supervision is required for Users under the age of 18. If we learn that one of our Users is under 13, we will delete his/her account as soon as possible. If you think that one of our users is under 13, please contact us. 

## Advertisement

The advertisement on the Website is covered by the Google AdSense program. Google's AdSense program uses the [DoubleClick DART](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/) cookie. Google's use of the DART cookie enables this Website to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/). 

## Cookies

Cookies are used to store your personal preferences when you visit a website. When you access Favorise, we send one or more cookies to your computer to provide you with a better user experience. The website uses cookies to know your location to provide you with your local news. However, you can disable your cookies directly on the settings of your web browser if you wish. 

## User Information

We store your IP address in our database when you vote to accurately count the number of votes. We also keep the information on your web browser hashed (encrypted). We use the tool Piwik in order to build statistics on our web traffic. If you want more information on Piwik, please click [here](http://piwik.org/). 

## Content

For all the Content you post on our Website that is covered by intellectual property (for example, your comments, links, personal picture or video), you give us a non-exclusive, transferable, sub-licensable, royalty-free, worldwide license to use any of that information. 

When you delete your account, all your personal information will be deleted from our current database. It is possible that a copy of your information will remain in some of our backups for a reasonable period of time. However, this information will no longer be available to the public and will only be conserved by Favorise INC. The comments you posted will not be removed from our website. However, you can remove your username by sending an email at [accounts@favorise.com](mailto:accounts@favorise.com) with your request.
